[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":68540,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":207486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":10801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":218290,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":3897,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":222190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":5281,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":227473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2223,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":229698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":10927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":240627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1933,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":242563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3718,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":246282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1627,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":247911,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum  is 6 or  bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":252431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1193,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":253626,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["3","2"],"rt":7131,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":260759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1294,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":262054,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4059,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":266114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":2241,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":268357,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Reme mber, to  perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":271603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1253,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":272858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":275410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1400,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":276811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":280979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1191,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":282171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":30022,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":312196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub >). Simi larly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":49434,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":361632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":21316,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":382951,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":13458,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":396411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the in verse of  an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4440,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":400852,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":10712,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":411566,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":416989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1541,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":418532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3621,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":422153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1017,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":423172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</s ub>? <br  /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":7960,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":431132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":13799,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":444932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":35074,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":480007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":70652,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":550660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an eleme nt which  can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":18381,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":569044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":24940,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":593985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5424,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":599411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's inc orrect.  5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":46205,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":645617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":63384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":709003,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 =  4, 2 = 4  +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":11351,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":720355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":9247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":729603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":13023,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":742627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9< /sub>, o n the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":68024,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":810653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":6350,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":817004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":8975,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":825980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What i s 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4754,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":830734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5598,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":836333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5536,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":841871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4877,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":846749,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":852669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I added 4+1, which equals 5. Since 5 is less than 9, it stays at 5. So the answer = 5.","response_history":["I added 4+1, which e","I added 4+1, which = 5. ","I added 4+1, which = 5.","I added 4+1, which = 5","I added 4+1, which = ","I added 4+1, which =","I added 4+1, which equals 5. s","I added 4+1, which equals 5. Since 5 is less than 9, it stays at 5. So the answer is ","I added 4+1, which equals 5. Since 5 is less than 9, it stays at 5. So th e answer  is","I added 4+1, which equals 5. Since 5 is less than 9, it stays at 5. So the answer i","I added 4+1, which equals 5. Since 5 is less than 9, it stays at 5. So the answer = 5."],"rt":60599,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":913270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8+4=12. Since 12 is more than 9 I have to subtract 9. 12-9=3. ","response_history":["8+4=12. Since 12 is more than 9 I have to subjec","8+4=12. Since 12 is more than 9 I have to subje","8+4=12. Since 12 is more than 9 I have to subj","8+4=12. Since 12 is more than 9 I have to subtract 9. 12-9 ","8+4=12. Since 12 is more than 9 I have to subtract 9. 12-9=3. "],"rt":46206,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":959479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What i s the id entity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"I think the identity is 0, because whatever you combine it with you get the same thing back.","response_history":["I think the identiy","I think the identity ","I think the identity","I think the identit","I think the identi","I think the identity is 0, because whatever you combine it with you get the same thing bac.","I think the identity is 0, because whatever you combine it with you get the same thing back."],"rt":159782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1119262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":38374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1157639,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 1-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1162045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The answer is 6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I then have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","response_history":["6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is eauq","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is eau","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is ea","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to or greater tah","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to or greater ta","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to or greater than ","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to or","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to o","6, beca use 3+6= 9. Since 9 is equal to ","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, Ihave t","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, Ihave ","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, Ihave","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, Ihav","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, Iha","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, Ih","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subj","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0. ","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0.","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0  ","6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","T6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The 6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equa ls 0 (th e identity).","The a6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The an6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The ans6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answe6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer 6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer i6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer is6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer is 6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer is 6, becaus e 3+6=9.  Since 9 is equal to 9, I thave to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer is 6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I thhave to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer is 6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I thehave to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer is 6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I thenhave to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity).","The answer is 6, because 3+6=9. Since 9 is equal to 9, I then have to subtract 9, which equals 0 (the identity)."],"rt":83403,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1245451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 through 8. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2+2=8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, etc.","response_history":["Yes. o=","Yes. o","Yes. 0=2=2=","Yes. 0=2=2","Yes. 0=2=","Yes. 0=2+2+2+2+2+2+2+","Yes. 0=2","Yes. 0=","Yes. 0","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the number between 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers between 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers etween 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers tween 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers ween 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers een 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers en 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers n 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers  0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 and 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and re ached al l the numbers 0 nd 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 d 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0  8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 t 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 th 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 thr 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 thro 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 throu 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 throug 8","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 through 8. For example, 2=2","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 through 8. For example, 2=","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 through 8. For example, 2+2=4, 2=2=2","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple ti mes and  reached all the numbers 0 through 8. For example, 2+2=4, 2=2=","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 through 8. For example, 2+2=4, 2=2","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 through 8. For example, 2+2=4, 2=","Yes. I added 2 to itself multiple times and reached all the numbers 0 through 8. For example, 2+2=4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2+2=8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, etc."],"rt":314891,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1560344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, you can only get 0,3 & 6 by adding 3 to itself: 3=3, 3+3=6, 3+3+3=9(-9)=0.","response_history":["No, you can only get 0,3 ^ ","No, you can only get 0,3 ^","No, you can only get 0,3 & 6 by adding 3 to itself. ","No, you can only get 0,3 & 6 by adding 3 to i tself.","No, you can only get 0,3 & 6 by adding 3 to itself: 3=3, 3+3=6, 3+3+3=99","No, you can only get 0,3 & 6 by adding 3 to itself: 3=3, 3+3=6, 3+3+3=9(-9)=0."],"rt":123048,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1683395,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5+5+5=6, 5+5+5+5=2, etc.","response_history":["Yes. By adding 5 to itself you cn","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of th ","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbe ","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5=5=5","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5=5=","Yes. By adding 5 to itself y ou can m ake all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5=5","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5=","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5+5+5=6, 5=5=5","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5+5+5=6, 5=5=","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5+5+5=6, 5=5","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5+5+5=6, 5=","Yes. By adding 5 to itself you can make all of the numbers from 0-8. For example, 5=5, 5+5=1, 5+5+5=6, 5+5+5+5=2, etc."],"rt":216130,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1899528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. You can only make the numbers 0, 3 & 6 from adding 6 to itself.","response_history":["No, ","No,","No. You can only make then","No. You can only make the numbers 0, 3 & 6 from adding 6 o","No. You can only make the numbers 0, 3 & 6 from adding 6 yo ","No. You can only make the numbers 0, 3 & 6 from adding 6 yo","No. You can only make the numbers 0, 3 & 6 from adding 6 y","No. You can only make the numbers 0, 3 & 6 from adding 6 to itself."],"rt":82247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1981778,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":80821,"trial_type":"instruc tions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2062602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"Inverse = +_n - 1. ","response_history":["The","Th","T","Inverse = +_n-","Inverse = +_n - 1. "],"rt":190310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2252914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the previous answer wrong now.)","response_history":["The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the forumula ","The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the forumula","The  inverse  is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the forumul","The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the forumu","The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the forum","The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the foru","The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the formula would be +_n-x","The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the formula would be +_n-","The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the formula would be +_n x","The inverse is what is added to x to equal +_n. So the formula would be +_n - x. ","The inverse is what is added to x to equal _n. So the formula would be +_n - x. ","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be +_n - x. ","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be _n - x. ","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the prefvious ","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula  would be  n - x. (I can see that I got the prefvious","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the prefviou","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the prefvio","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the prefvi","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the prefv","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the pref","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the previous answer wrong now)","The inverse is what is added to x to equal n. So the formula would be n - x. (I can see that I got the previous answer wrong now.)"],"rt":138646,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2391562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13 -0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"There may be a pattern, but I wasn't able to figure it out.","response_history":["There may be a pap","There may be a pattern, but I wasn't able to figure it out."],"rt":67582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2459147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":17646,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2476796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must  not be a  generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":8790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2485587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":30631,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2516219,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"That sounds correct/true, but I am not exactly sure why it is correct.","response_history":["Tha t sounds o","That sounds correct, but I am not exactly sure wha","That sounds correct, but I am not exactly sure why it is correct.","That sounds correct , but I am not exactly sure why it is correct.","That sounds correct, but I am not exactly sure why it is correct.","That sounds correct/, but I am not exactly sure why it is correct.","That sounds correct/t, but I am not exactly sure why it is correct.","That sounds correct/tr, but I am not exactly sure why it is correct.","That sounds correct/tru, but I am not exactly sure why it is correct.","That sounds correct/true, but I am not exactly sure why it is correct."],"rt":74747,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2590967,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Alway s","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":148867,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2739838,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself (with the +_n) will create all the numbers that comprise n.","response_history":["Yesm, ","Yesm,","Yesm","Yes, because if x is a generator then by addition","Yes, because if x is a generator then by additio","Yes, because if x is a generator then by additi","Yes, because if x is a generator then by addit","Yes, because if x is a generator then by addi","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itese","Yes, because if x is a generator then b y adding  it to ites","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to ite","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to iteslf","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itesl","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to ites","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to ite","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself in the","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself in th","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself in t","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself in ","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself in","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself i","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself (with the x","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself (with the +_n) will create all the number s","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself (with the +_n) will c reate al l the number ","Yes, because if x is a generator then by adding it to itself (with the +_n) will create all the numbers that comprise n."],"rt":203396,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2943235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":15415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2958652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2370,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2961023,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your a ge?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"52","response_history":["52"],"rt":3812,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2964837,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2968638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I had  calculu s many years ago but I was terrible at it and don't remember a single thing. ","response_history":["I had calu","I had calculau","I had calcula","I had calculus mak","I had calculus many years ago but I was terrb","I had calculus many years ago but I was terrible at it and od","I had calculus many years ago but I was terrible at it and o","I had calculus many years ago but I was terrible at it and dn","I had calculus many years ago but I was terrible at it and don't remember a sing ","I had calculus many years ago but I was terrible at it and don't remember a single thing. "],"rt":59190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3027829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, r emember  and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3034666,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":7961,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3042628,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - som ewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":6112,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3048741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":7190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3055932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5511,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3061445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":3750,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3065196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":23440,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3088637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, I used pen and paper to help with the calculations for the generators.","response_history":["Yes.","Yes, I used pen and paper to help with the calculations for the genra","Yes, I used pen and paper to help with the calculations for the genr","Yes, I used pen and paper to help with  the calc ulations for the generators."],"rt":28118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3116757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It was interesting. It was much more enjoyable at the beginning for me. When it got more theoretical I had a harder time following the logic.","response_history":["This was interesting. ","This was interesting.","his was interesting.","is was interesting.","s was interesting."," was interesting.","I was interesting.","It was interesting. It was much more enjoyable at the beginning for me. When it goe ","It was interesting. It was much more enjoyable at the beginning for me. When it goe","It was interesting. It was much more enjoyable at the beginning for me. When it got mor ","It was interesting. It was much more enjoyable at the beginning for me. When it got more theorethi","It was inter esting.  It was much more enjoyable at the beginning for me. When it got more theoreth","It was interesting. It was much more enjoyable at the beginning for me. When it got more theoretical I had a harder time following the logic."],"rt":51878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3168636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]